Dr. Po-Hsun Tseng

6+ years experience of large-scale software development with C programming on the Linux system throughout my Ph.D. journey.

Seeking a challenging and rewarding opportunity with low-level system programming

(eg. device driver, Linux kernel, CPU architecture) to apply my skills at a fabless company.



CONTACT

zengbs@gmail.com

+886 966 587 832

Hsinchu, Taiwan

https://github.com/zengbs

SKILLS

Programming

C Bash scripting System programming CUDA Python

Operating System

Linux - user Linux - kernel

Architecture

ARM architecture

Software & Tools

Git Vim Gdb Valgrind

Languages

Chinese (native)
English – writing
English – speaking
English – listening
English – reading



6 08/2016 - 06/2022

♀ National Taiwan University, Taiwan

Ph.D. in Computational Physics

WORK HISTORY

12/2014 - 01/2016

♥ TDK corporation, Singapore Design surface acoustic wave(SAW) filters

1 08/2013 - 08/2014

♥ Military Service

Circuit designer

EDUCATION

1 09/2011 - 07/2013

♀ National Taiwan University, Taiwan

1 09/2006 - 07/2011

National Central University, Taiwan

M.Sc. in Physics

B.Sc. in Mathematics

ACHIEVEMENT

My first achievement

GENERAL SKILLS

Numerical algorithm

Large-scale project

cscope

makefile

GNU autotools

PUBLICATIONS

An adaptive mesh, GPU-accelerated, and error minimized special relativistic hydrodynamics code

Po-Hsun Tseng, Hsi-Yu Schive, Tzihong Chiueh

₩ 2021

Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society Vol. 504, pp. 3298-3315

% ADS, arXiv

TALKS

• An adaptive-mesh, GPU-accelerated, and optimally error-controlled special relativistic hydrodynamics code Oral (remote), American Center for Physics College Park, U.S.A

Mar. 2021

A new and accurate code for simulating special relativistic hydrodynamics
 Oral, Annual Meeting of the Physical Society of Taiwan, NPTU.

Feb. 2020

REFERENCES

- Please send an appointment letter to request a call. $\ref{eq:posterior}$
- Dr. Tzihong Chiueh

Distinguished Professor, Institute of Astrophysics, National Taiwan University

- ▼ Taipei 10617, Taiwan
- chiuehth@phys.ntu.edu.tw
- **** +886 2 3366 8628
- Dr. Hsi-Yu Schive

Assistant Professor, Institute of Astrophysics, National Taiwan University

- Taipei 10617, Taiwan
- hyschive@phys.ntu.edu.tw
- +886 2 3366 8644
- Dr. Hsiang-Yi Karen Yang

Assistant Professor, Institute of Astronomy, National Tsing Hua University

- Hsinchu 30013, Taiwan
- hyang@phys.nthu.edu.tw
- **4886** 3 574 2953